Aleksei Osinnii

Senior Front-end Developer

Highly motivated, experienced, accurate developer with almost 5 years production background in creating various web pages, Node.js applications. Constantly looking forward for a new opportunities and competitions.

Contacts

+79099893808 | markcavalli@mail.ru | https://linkedin.com/in/markcavalli | https://markcavalli.github.io

Work Experience (5 years)

Senior Front-end Developer, **Promsvyazbank** (Nov 2021 - now)

- HTML, CSS, Angular, Reactive Forms, Typescript, Landing page.
- Create landing pages, working on main website.

Typescript Developer, **OnMoon** (Sep 2019 – Nov 2021, 2 years 2 months)

- Typescript, HTML, CSS, Vue, Vue-Router, VueX, Node, Postgres, typeorm.
- Built Grand Theft Auto 5 multiplayer server (Server, Client, UI-Interface)

JavaScript Developer, **Gamedev Startup** (Apr 2019 – Aug 2019, 5 months)

- HTML, CSS, Vue, Vue-Router, VueX, Node, MongoDB, JavaScript.
- Built Grand Theft Auto 5 multiplayer server (Server, Client, UI-Interface)

JavaScript Developer, Adacta (Mar 2019 – Apr 2019, 2 months)

- JavaScript, JSON, Angular.
- Worked on a service for insurance companies (Raiffeisen mostly).

Junior Front-end Developer, **BKC-ih** (Feb 2018 – Mar 2019, 1 year 2 months)

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Vue.
- Worked on main website, emails, landing-pages.

Education (5,5 years)

Design of technological machines and complexes, **Specialist - Engineer**, The Moscow State University of Technology "STANKIN" (september 2012 - june 2018)

Introduction

Here is a short version of my journey. If you want to know more about my work challenges and pet-projects, feel free to visit my website: https://markcavalli.github.io

About me

Acquaintance with the web and websites began at 16, when I created the first website, where I learned the basics of HTML and CSS. The first site was quite successful: at its peak, attendance was 1,500 visitors per day. Then admission to university, where I studied for 5.5 years.

In my last study year, I saw that an analog of SAMP from GTA SA was being created in GTA 5, and since then I have started studying node.js, because the server part of the multiplayer was on it. After university, I got a job at the VKS company as a HTML-developer. I made up landing pages, mailing lists... HTML, CSS, jQuery. I was alone of the developers there, so after a year I wanted to receive feedback on the code, work in a team with more experienced teammates.

That's how I found a job in Adakta's company. At that time, I rewrote the structure of the GTA 5 pet project many times, started the development of the server in open source:

https://github.com/MarkCavalli/rageserver . Then I realized that most people are not going to contribute to the project, but are just waiting for it to open their own server based on mine. I also ran into technical limitations. Then I started a new project, transferring it to Vue.js SPA with VueX and VueRouter. I also started using typescript on the server and client side.

At this time, the guys wrote to me, offered to develop a GTA 5 server on a commercial basis, and I agreed. It was a startup that didn't pay enough attention to the architecture and code format, so after 6 months I burned out and decided to leave.

Then I was found by guys from a similar GTA 5 project (OnMoon), and I got a job offer. We have been developing our product quite successfully using PostgreSQL as a database, typescript on the server and Vue on the client. It was a great company where I worked for a more than 2 years, but then decided to go forward to a new skills.

At the moment I am working at PromsvyazBank, where I switched to a new Angular stack for myself, adapted within a month, now I am completely immersed in development.